[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "What do you think the movie industry reaction is to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, it's just tragic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "ROFT, 60 MINUTES CORRESPONDENT: So this was drugs or alcohol or both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "NNP", ":", "RB", "DT", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Yes, all that stuff, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "And why did you decide to stop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "You panic, you panic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "What was he like as a man, for people who didn't know Philip Seymour Hoffman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "He was a very private man, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Philip Seymour Hoffman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "As an actor, what made him so special?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "I think actors, I mean he opened up to them actually, as private as he was, he opened up to his peers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Woody"]}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What do you think of these claims and charges from Dylan Farrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, first of all, I've known Woody for a really long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dylan Farrow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "I'm getting through to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "So, there's never anything illegal about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Why do you think that Mia Farrow is helping her daughter and she's been backed by her son Ronan and (inaudible), why do you think they're going through all of this if they had simply all invented it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "JJR", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mia Farrow", "Ronan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "So, you personally have no issue with what he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Oh no, no, no, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "What exactly did she asked you to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, it wasn't Mia herself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "''", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "What is your recollection at that period because that seems to be the crucial element really of -- everything has blown up again this week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, I recollected very well, I wrote about it, I have a chapter in my book, \"Taking the Stand\" about the case, and I went back and read all the transcripts in order to prepare for writing the books.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "So did you believed her at that time when she told you about the abuse allegations involving Dylan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I had no reason to disbelieve.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dylan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Is it still possible for Woody Allen to face any charges or has statute limitations now expired in this particular kind of case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Statute limitation is almost certainly expired.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Woody Allen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allan Dershowitz"]}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Why do you believe them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Well, first let me just point about Allan Dershowitz, that he is a lawyer here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "That's not in dispute, either but the two facts I wanted to put here just ask you your impression really is when -- is there any way of assessing the character of Woody Allen when you take that fact and you take the fact that Allen to be somebody who's now having an affair with when he was 42 and he found this girl, 17, on the set of one of his movies and so you (inaudible) with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "CC", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Woody Allen", "Allen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "When you put them both together, is it inappropriate enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Do you think there is something wrong with (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "But you're doing this wrong because what you're saying is that this is a man who had -- had a relationship that you might call inappropriate, not illegal and therefore, then this is the leap that you're making here whether you're saying it or not, therefore, it's likely he molested a seven-year old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael", "Michael"]}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Have you ever been attracted to an 18-year-old woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Michael, I'm in a bizarre -- Michael, I'm in this composition of...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Have you ever been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "... having to jump in an answer a question on my own show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 503, "question": "... who knows?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Some would say a lot of...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "But what I was saying is because you don't know that it didn't happen either, do you, in the same position as me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "You know, Piers, I don't know that you haven't molested someone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "What should we make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "LOOM: Well, first of all, I've never met anybody in this case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]